makes you look short bro
all right what's up guys welcome back to
another episode center forget podcast so
i mean this was very special to me
honestly because you guys know i haven't
actually haven't done a trader podcast
probably in like two two or three
episodes i've been kind of you know
doing a bunch of different entrepreneurs
and i'm like you know what let's take it
back to uh some traders but let's take
it back to somebody that can be like
just like you guys right coming up on
their journey so i'm like who better
than fernando right so fernando's
actually one of my top students um from
the boot camp you guys might recognize
him because i pop up a little picture of
a meme with him i said he's a threat to
the markets because um he flipped 1500
to 3 000 in the house how many days well
the first time you put it was um i
remember you it was in the booth i was
like i'm gonna choose one whoever flips
it right yeah and then i was like oh
[__] okay expect words that's fine
doesn't matter yeah that's fine
i was like oh [__] i was okay and then i
got the athens i was like get in athens
you open a open uh
uh what's it called an account an
account yeah and then um
i got in i got i think it was gbchf i
put 45 i was like yo it is what it is
you know i got it i woke up the next
morning it was up i was up seven
thousand well i was i was i was up
six thousand and seven a thousand in
floating profit right and then i did
that and i was like you know let me see
if i can take it at 10k and that's when
i posted on the boot camp i was up at 7
000 you saw the screenshot was up 7 000
and then um i don't know two trades
later because i wasn't really following
the strategy i was just doing it and
then um
i was losing when i was like you know
what i'm staying here i'm not i'm not
touching it no more so that's i was that
and i did it like in two days actually
or two days two days yeah i remember
because i was i was like you you posted
a screen show like oh like i'm done i'm
gonna leave it here yeah and then
everybody else i think some other guy
you know blew it he think he raised 100
percent and then i think it was
cleveland shout out to cleveland he uh
i think he was up by like like 2k so i
mean i know you passed i mean you didn't
pass you you flipped it from 15 to 3k
and then you're up how much in your
challenge right now right now i'm up
seven thousand percent i'm seven
thousand seven percent that's how do you
feel like how do you feel i don't know
it's like bro i mean before the boot
camp i was i wasn't really like i don't
know trading wise like i right the way i
see the markets now is not how i used to
see it before like i appreciate that for
that and um i don't know just like
everything i see in the market i was
just wait completely different like i
don't know i feel like i'm profit i
already told you it's like there's
antennae i feel profitable already i
remember so it's pretty cool i mean it
feels like it's something you work for
you know so it feels it feels good
yeah so fernando's one of my he was part
of my second bootcamp i've only done two
boot camps and like you can tell when
somebody really wants it right because
like you had your camera on all the time
yeah i had your camera yeah
i remember you yeah i fixed it i finally
fixed it i was like
whatever whenever i would be like yo
fernando i break down your charts it was
like glitching i'm like
give me give me the whole like two two
fernando's there you took a picture one
time i remember yeah so um
he like like you can tell when somebody
wants it back because he was as soon as
i dropped the zoom code it'd be sanchez
cleveland's um uh was all the trailer
that i had last time felipe felipe and
then fernando like as soon as i dropped
the zoom code so like you can tell when
somebody wants it right always asking
questions and stuff so like i mean where
were you before like you're trading now
how like how are you going into the
markets right because like i feel like a
lot of people can relate to you because
you're just coming up right now on your
trading you got me so like where were
you like let's say six months ago well
six months ago um i was like i was kind
of like a day trade i wasn't really like
a swing trader like that um back then i
would just try to get in the markets
i'll go in
maybe two hours like felipe like two
hours like he said before two hours one
hour trying to look for a trade i didn't
see anything i was like all right
whatever it is what it is and i was just
my risk management wasn't there at all
either so i appreciate that and then
you're psychology of it really helped me
a lot well that's right college of
course yeah you had that and then that
helped me a lot too with my trades
and yeah man i don't know
like the way that you set up everything
because this this boot camp you did it
more organized back then you said you
put everything in this was more like
organized like the third day the first
day i was like
i don't know 2 000. yeah because i told
you i don't know if you remember i tell
you like the one i had before was like
everything was rules based i don't think
you understood me though but you're like
yeah it's the same thing i was like damn
i think i just lost two thousand dollars
yeah and then this it was the third day
i was like you started breaking out like
the
the type of correlation i was like yo i
don't remember i was like with my head i
remember yeah what the [__] i was like
yo that's crazy and then that now it's
like like he said i'm seven i'm up seven
percent on my um 100k and once i get it
because i normally pass it like i tell
you already i feel profitable yeah
thanks to you so yeah i mean my training
changes a lot i feel profitable already
and i appreciate you for it no no 100
and i i appreciate you because like not
only for investing into like the
bootcamp like that's whatever you see
like for me yeah yeah and like i mean
like for you to like be there you get me
because it's like i'd be dropping the
zoom code some people are like in the
gym or some people are like you know not
even getting on so like that you were on
there every single time you went that to
me showed me you respect my time and ah
so i i appreciate you friends i mean
yeah what do you what do you got coming
now right like i mean like because
obviously the the verification if you do
bro for me if you pass the challenge you
could pass a verification i mean like
it's like you just do it again by half
right so like how are you gonna approach
the verification the verification um i
mean this whole time i was doing two
percent i really never did one percent
until the verification wise um i
probably i'm gonna do one percent
because awfully like all you really need
is like one trade and it's one to three
all the time
so i probably get like a one to one i
mean uh one percent once i get that one
percent i'll risk i'll go three percent
because if i lose that three percent
it's going to be well like i'm just back
to break even because one two three it's
like risk three percent the next time
and yeah i'll probably probably pass it
already
what was like one of your first like
biggest struggles when you started off
trading
struggles entries bro your entries
entries like the way you explained the
answer oh that's right because like i
say that for like the last of the
bootcamp remember like because i i would
give you guys like the basically like 70
and then the last week is where i
explained together the structure like
the little trick with the structure yeah
that changed everything bro
that was the first day when i saw i was
like it's like something you should know
about like yeah if the if the daily goes
up you know the four hour has to change
to go bullets you know so
i saw that i was just like wow like it's
something you should know but you don't
really realize it yeah yeah i don't know
so that happened i was like damn i was
like wow i never really saw it like that
and that's one of the
yeah just pretty nice and then well i
mean
other than trading what did you do
before like now like are you full-time
trading now are you like i'm getting
online so under backstory um so
january is when i um i was working two
days two days a week i told my boss look
i'm gonna focus a little more on the
markets so it was january i started two
days a week i did that for like
two months three months when was the
boot camp number two march something uh
like march somewhere
so march uh march came i saw i saw the
little boot camp number two you were
saying then i said i said felipe's boo
kamehameha he was like 25 percent when
we got down there must be some gems in
there
you know okay you saw the podcast yeah
yeah yeah yeah yeah that's what that's
what sold me okay because i was if
you're getting it but then i fell in
love like yeah i'm getting it definitely
so that's that and um i was doing
construction because i don't know like i
don't really care about this like i
still have my visa
okay i'm from there's and i'm i'm
starting i'm a visa together by this
year or next year you're from honduras
right now i'm from india okay nice yeah
and um well i don't have my visa yeah
everything is under my dad's account
okay yeah you don't care you could put
that on really yeah yeah
and yeah bro yo i just blanked out what
was the question
[Laughter]
[Music]
so then i saw your boot camp and um i
was working two days and then i saw it
coming up and i and as soon as it was
the first week i told you about hey look
i'm not gonna work i work one full
weekend i was working two days only and
then the week the two weeks of the
bootcamp i was like
um i'm not gonna i'm gonna work this
full week and i'm not gonna work two
weeks because that full week i already
paid for my because i kept my expenses
low so that that four week of me working
i made like a thousand every every every
every week off construction
so that full week um i recovered for
like what a month of me because uh yeah
a month of me working so once it came i
was like yeah i'll be back in two weeks
i took my boss right oh you get you gave
him the the two week notice
i'm gonna be back in two weeks and then
two weeks him like i said bro i feel
profit all night and then he called me
coming back i was like nah nah i'm
making some money off the market i light
him because i know he's gonna pressure
me to go yeah because one of his best
workers there now yeah that's that and
then i stopped upside he stopped um
going so what was the last time you
worked uh when we started the boot camp
that was the last time yeah oh [__] yeah
and right now i'm living off of because
after high school i saved up 15 thousand
dollars i'm living off that right now
with my place how do you know 21. oh wow
same same age yeah bro so i mean like i
mean um
definitely take the leap of faith i did
it 100 you take the leave of faith
that's what he wanted bro yeah i mean
like i mean that that goes back to like
the point like you're getting on the
zooms you made the investment [__]
left your job you can't be like like
you're going all in you get me so i mean
like how did how did that feel like did
you have any like because i mean people
hit me up all the time like oh at any
point in time did you not want like did
you not want it did you quit or did you
have any thoughts of stopping and i'm
just like bro there was it was either i
was gonna make it i was gonna make it
you get me like hot like what what about
you like i mean like me uh i mean i
think zodiac because like a lot of
people wish to have supportive parents i
have supportive parents so like you
gotta do what you gotta do and like i
don't pay rent right now right now so um
yeah i had my supportive parents i like
she told me do what you got to do
and that's that but that's really that's
really dope though that you have
supportive parents because like even to
this day not that my parents aren't
supportive they just still don't
understand i mean like yeah they're just
spanning people you know they know it's
like hard work you know the harder you
work the more money you get where you
get they're like they don't know off
button over click a clip of a button
of a click of a button like you can make
money you know like mom like i turned
1500 into like seven thousand
two days yeah i could understand that
bro yeah you know hispanic parents yeah
so how did you get into trading like
what made you get into trading yeah i
mean so in ninth grade um it was um
ninth grade i mean nine ninth grade
twelve when i graduated high school you
know i've always wanted to be the top
one percent so
honestly i was always looking for stuff
i was i was going in computer how to
make money how to do this out of that
and then i came in through to modeling
this agency came up to me
i was like okay i paid two thousand
dollars for for um
they were teaching me how to walk
because i it was an actor thing too you
gotta walk a specific way yeah yeah like
it's because it's like yeah it's
aesthetics for um okay for modeling
because i wasn't i wasn't really fit
back then i i don't feel like me
personally like i'm looking pictures i'm
not photogenic in my opinion so that i
didn't really want to pursue it so i
left that aside then um then pandemic
came
and pandemic was like all my friends all
my friends we never really we didn't
have nothing to do everybody was just
home like working from home and stuff so
we started this on youtube channel so
that's we started doing that
and
and after that pandemic fast forward the
pandemic like people started going back
into the jobs and stuff and then
everybody was like nah whatever f
youtube and then i saw and then i saw
trading
i went you know i've been knew about
trading in 12th grade but then i went
back to trading and i was like oh
youtube is not going anywhere modeling
is not going nowhere anywhere so let me
just go back to trading you know and
then on
and then january i got into swaggy c's
um
little um
i'm gonna get swag on the podcast yeah
soon so i was i was with my second
mentor so i learned from something from
him i had some profits in there but i
feel like i still didn't know that why
you know
and then um then came the boot camp
which fast forward on
march
so that's that's what came into that's
where i'm at right now that's pretty
crazy so you kind of like kind of
started basically at the beginning of
the year and now you're kind of like on
that rise right now yeah bro and like
that bootcamp changed me changed
everything oh by the way i might do
another bootcamp if you guys might want
to do it there's a waiting waiting list
for application i'm going to have it
below if you guys want to do it
you have to know
i don't know but you just guys just do
it you know you see the results you see
like you know i was here like a couple
months ago now i'm here up seven percent
of my funded account and flipped 1500 to
3 000. no no i'm i'm telling you right
now if well i haven't i have no doubt i
mean the other traders that are going to
be in the the ring challenge with you
because you know you're going to go
against them if you win i'm going i'm
going to personally give you a 200k
account like from level up so you can go
ahead and trade it for i got you like
trust me i got you
all right so now that kind of like i
mean
because let's be realistic kind of like
swing trading kind of like the way we
trade now you don't really
you don't really got to be on the charts
that much time you got i mean so like
how does it like what do you do on your
free time right like how do you manage
your day since you're not working you're
just straight trading what do you do
so usually like what my days consist of
is like in the morning i usually um
let's say i'm in a trade like the day
before i enter a chat i just check how
it's going
if it's like i want to one i put it to
break even or if it happens that day
okay it happens and um
uh
and then from that from that i just
start like kind of just looking at
charge i kind of study a little bit i
back test a little bit for like an hour
or two and then i just go
probably watch some tv at 3 p.m i'll
head to the gym
come back check my trades how it's going
and um yeah i just back to that's
literally what my day consists of after
i quit my construction job that's all i
do because yeah i really want it you
know yeah i just like probably i would
say half of my day consists of just
studying the market fire so the more
hours i feel like the more hours you put
in the market like it's just some little
details like you can't explain i feel
like you know stuff that you can't
explain yeah in marketing because i mean
it's like it's like like the first thing
that i told you at the beginning i'm
like bro like i'm going to explain
things in the boot camp that it's not
going to make sense right now you got me
like you need that
time yeah like you got to be sitting
down there it's like for example let's
say let's say you want to be a pilot or
whatever in order for you to get your
pilot's license you have to have i think
it's like 100
200 hours of to be a pilot like you need
that air time experience you have to go
through a cloud you have to go through
some storms you got to go through like a
sunny day through like an engine failure
like you got to experience those things
you gotta be like i can tell you all
these things i can show you them but
then like and let's get experience like
you gotta literally like be in that
chair you gave me an experience so like
i mean how does it feel coming from
construction that's like a big shift bro
that's like we were working outside like
in the city yeah i was working outside i
was like it's like hard labor bro it's
like picking up like i used to do um
construction my job was on uh
concrete pumping it was like some two
like it was like
25 pound hoses you got to carry them
move them around all day do all that
coming from that honestly is like
it's it's i mean i mean it's amazing bro
like literally like i said you make
money from a click of a button like a
lot of people don't know about that yeah
some people think forex is a scam but
you just really got to put in the work
you know yeah it depends how you got
exposed to forex but
but yeah it's like it's a huge
difference like i really want this
lifestyle you know i can't wait to get
used to it so i mean like when we were
coming in earlier you know i'm like
maybe you're like a little bit nervous
right like it's like yes we pulled up to
raul's house because we had left the
camera they're like how does it like
feel like we're like we're normal people
yes yeah you know you know like it's
like a lot of people look up to you like
bro this this is people like seeing all
these people lamborghini all these
people seeing his cars like that stuff
he's like
i'll say i'm regular i know you think
you're a regular too but like to the
eyes of other people you're not regular
you're like yo you're like you yes you
are you could say you are bro but like
i'm not gonna say like an alien or
anything but like yo just like
people see you as like i don't know like
you're you're that top percent you're 21
like
it's just crazy you know seeing the
people you look up to and trading wise
you're you're with like the top earners
in forex in miami and seeing being here
seeing all these lives is like crazy to
me like bro i i've never been like this
is so much
professionality i don't even know that's
a word or anything
but i mean like like i mean because like
six months ago you were in construction
construction now now you're here like
does it like obviously it's worth the
journey of course it's like the journey
100 but like
it like feels real like this is possible
right like you you feel like you're
you're here like yeah i'm here like i
said it's just crazy to think about a
guy i look up to the guy
like the guy i just i learned from
seeing i would have never thought i was
going to be in this podcast like no it's
all about the hard work
am i really that short bro i'm not that
sure
you're just you're just talking [__] yo
this this guy this guy pulls up he
literally pulls up and i'm like
oh my god what are you telling me i'm
about to return but i got another trader
and i i told him i'm like bro we got to
get another trader bro this guy he's
he's not it doesn't fit in my car bro
so we went in the rolls we pulled up to
raul's house i'm like you want to pull
it to rails pick up the camera and like
you know i i could tell you know like i
could tell like you're excited you get
me so to kind of see that because like i
mean like i i personally like
people that i look up to you know like
that's happened to me you gave me so
seen that you and i i just want to make
you feel like you know like cool bro
like we're just normal people you know
we could bring you in be part of the
crew bro like you know it's it's lit i
mean yeah it's also like it gives you
motivation you know seeing like seeing
where you're at like a lot of like 20
i'm 21 see i want to be like where you
guys at like all the like have that like
mentality like hustle mentality all that
saying lamborghini all the cars there
was like yo like you want to be there
bro yeah that gives you more like
it gives you that urge to like be great
well i mean i'm gonna be honest with you
you're ahead of me bro time wise like
bro i've been training now literally
about to be like literally middle of
this year is gonna be four years bro six
months and you're already like passing a
challenge because secondly you
technically you've only been training
for about six months but when i was six
months i was still like bro like how do
i identify this trend you know what i
mean i was still like bro how do i like
properly adjust all your stuff so bro
trust me time-wise you're ahead of me
bro yeah but it's just hard working you
said like time in the market where you
put in that like there's stuff you can't
explain that's why i do it like like the
nuances like the little details like
that you can't explain you just gotta
experience it you know talking about the
mars what was one of your biggest losses
did you ever lose a lot of money me me
personally i was never that type of guy
to go in all in i did a very like um
very um
mellow conserve conservatively i did it
like that and um so i i usually i blew
one account which was a hundred dollars
and then i did it again it was like i
didn't blow it again but like i put
another account over a hundred dollars
and then i took that account to 100 to
217. i was like i was doing the math
that's like 117 yeah like imagine having
100k that's 127 000 yeah in a span of a
month i was listening five percent ten
percent i didn't really know risk
management like that but the fact that i
did that gave me more motivation to like
you know what let me learn this bro like
this you can literally make money off
this you know so yeah i did that and
then that just gave me a whole lot of
motivation
that's that and then so what was like
one of your bigger wins uh biggest wins
was bro this is a story right so this is
when i was in swaggy sees um so i
entered a trade i re i think it was
i entered it was like a five percent
risk trade and my deal was like a
hundred dollars it was a hundred dollar
account no it was it was 217 and i got
32 dollars and i started doing the math
i'm like bro this is like what like five
thousand dollars in like if you have a
higher account bro i put some reggaeton
i was dancing all over the i'm not even
lying anywhere i was dancing all over
the house like i was so excited like i
even like my eyes got watery that time
was like bro i've been working
construction for like what four years
and i've seen this the way you can make
money in the market is just crazy
seeing all that i was like damn it's
like it's you know 32 dollars but like
let's say i had a higher account it
would be like five thousand seven
thousand dollars in one day i don't make
that in like four months you know mm-hmm
so it was just like it was cool right
and then
biggest loss-wise as well and that's
what like i guess when you get a big
glass of water people just back down
they're out there i don't want to train
no more bro and i was like
but i knew you could make money off it
so all i had to do was get the right
mentor thanks to you and um
so that's that then i i think i lost
seventeen dollars and then i lost
seventeen dollars two two days straight
i was like damn bro like what the i
thought i was doing good but that's like
that's psychology wise it's just like
bro like people don't know their
strategy their strategy works until like
you get two losses they just get like
they get down like oh this [__] don't
work no more for me you know so that's
that and then i didn't and then i just
fast forward to this the boot camp just
really helped me yeah that's crazy yeah
i i feel like people because like i mean
like i told you guys from the beginning
like my strategy let's say i have
anywhere from let's say my win rate is
right yeah which is realistic that's
amazing let's say even 50 percent like
that is still solid
let's say it's 50 for example it's
persistent and i'll lose five trades in
a row i know that my other five winning
trades are right around the corner but
you never know when they're gonna come
first you never know if you're gonna win
five trades first or lose five trades
first or if you win lose win lose win
lose the secret is risk to reward you
gotta have that positive risk to reward
well one two three yeah so i feel like a
lot of people will happen is when
they're like when they're in like the
learning phase of the strategy they'll
either hit those five winners at the
beginning and then they're like oh this
[__] doesn't work then they're going to
switch to another one you get me and
then that's basically like bro you were
about to hit the winning streak and then
they're basically you go downhill
because you weren't patient enough for
that point to come into your trading
right so i mean like every even if i
have
a 30 win rate i showed you guys the
examples in the charts even with 30 yeah
like i literally lost like seven trades
in a row and with the three trades i
make it back and i'm still positive
three yeah you're up like yeah that's
straight literally up what three three
i'll be up two percent
because three times three is nine right
yeah
yeah like i feel like that's what a lot
of people kind of do they kind of just
like jump the gun they're like oh wow i
lost five trades in a row trader and and
that's where the whole scam thing comes
like oh you're a scammer training
champion so they're not putting the work
you know yeah i think like they already
got it like no you really gotta put in
the work put in the time
what would you kind of recommend to
somebody out there working construction
learning how to trade like like get like
where you were let's just say six seven
months ago what would you tell you six
months ago if they're watching right now
or what i would tell myself someone yeah
believe it or not but i've always been
off some uh optimistic so i literally
have a video of me in construction
talking about um i don't know how i was
gonna do it i'll show you probably put
it up yeah bro we'll put it up huh
reporting this on a thursday july 24th
it's 8 47 even two years you're gonna
see where i'm at i'm tired of this i'm
like waking up i said five in the
morning
um helmet i had a face covering talking
about yo in two years you're gonna see
where i'm at i'm tired of this i'm tired
of this
and then
and the two years from now it's july 23
july 23rd right two years on july 23rd
look where i'm at like two years ago i
was i was telling myself on the phone
look you're gonna be here i even told
myself it was a video of me saying oh
you're gonna be an impulsive in three
years from now logan pause thing
but
and positive the podcast different from
yeah from logan i mean this is close
enough right now
so yeah two years ago and then two years
july 23 bro by july 23 i'm probably
gonna have my first 10 20k withdrawal i
know it for a heart you know i feel like
it's there uh-huh so by july 23 like bro
that video put in that video where like
my 20k withdrawal i'm gonna show you two
bro like i feel like i got it already
like i know my 20k withdraws coming from
ftmo by july 23rd i know i have that
that's dope so yeah i have that
confidence thanks to you bro that boot
camp really helped me a lot like if
you're really looking into like the boot
camp thing
i feel like yo it was not a waste of
money like if you really want it trust
me coming for me a construction guy
like
if you really want it you'll get it and
like that boot camp really helped me a
lot
com completely changing the whole weight
i trade forex
and like [__] bro i'm probably i'm
probably not even gonna do the boot camp
i just let him do the class
i'll let him take care of july 23 and
that 20k withdrawal coming you're going
to see july 23 this year this year's the
two years of that video i made oh wow
so bro we're right around the corner
yeah bro wow that's crazy
you gotta manifest no but like i'm
telling you like that's crazy because
you could literally pass your challenge
well like your past challenge whatever
this week next week right i mean you're
floating right now in profit right and
the trade you're in let me check right
now yeah if you could pop up a tree
right now in profit it's like i'm
opening the boot camp i'll open up some
other spots
i'll open up some other spots let's see
if you think you could get it right
let's see you're improving a thousand
dollars oh yeah that's good
i'm enough a thousand dollars
and um right now yeah if i get this
trade i already passed my um i mean mine
i've been passed it i had 10k already
i'll show you i'll show you right now
i've been had 10k
but i didn't know that you could put the
0.01 and you in the two day and i saw a
video i started watching all your videos
bro i still watching from bro there's so
many gems bro people don't know you
gotta really go back and really search
for them bro zero point zero one i
didn't know i counted as a day i started
playing one percent on trace that i
didn't even make sense because for me
not to miss the night the ten day um
thing the minimum trading day that's i
didn't want to miss it that's why i put
it one percent and i went right now i
was at 10 percent and then
and then i went down to seven percent i
was putting random trades wow i didn't
want to miss the days that's why i'm up
seven percent now all right i've been
passing though okay that's fine
so i mean that that's kind of crazy you
say that that july 23rd i mean bro we
could get you like on a part two for
sure because like
it's kind of crazy because
you you're about to pass basically
i mean i saw the momentum on that trade
i think i think you'd be good um so you
passed a challenge beginning of june
let's say you finish the verification
mid-june you start trading the funded
mid-june and then your withdrawal will
be coincidentally right at the middle of
july 23rd that's kind of crazy how all
of that could kind of play out bro yeah
that's pretty scary you're not going to
right he's like i don't know it seems
pretty cool yeah i thought it was like
it could really happen yeah and it's
going to happen so um other other than
trading like you you have like any
cryptos like like like this do any of
those other things kind of entertain you
because you know there was like a big
nfc boom i mean i kind of backed out a
little bit not gonna lie me personally
the first thing i got introduced to was
forex i didn't really uh like not like i
was never into those futures cryptos not
really i don't really understand it like
i feel like that's just for the time i
might be wrong but i feel like that's
just for the time being i just don't see
like uh the matter versus all that i
don't really i don't know but me
personally um once i say once i start
making money me is probably like for me
i like my future wise i feel like i just
properties you know yeah i feel like
that's where the money really like
compounds and that's where you grow you
can actually see your money yeah i mean
yeah i definitely like real estate
earlier i was uh yesterday i went to
play poker um at one of my buddies house
and then there was a real estate guy
there big big real estate guy and he was
saying real estate is not going to drop
like at least here in miami ever right
because he's like bro you could go to
you know queens in new york right i i've
never been to queens i don't know
anybody's like bro you can literally get
like a like i'm sorry but like a [__]
hole where like you're living with like
rats roaches and everything and you're
gonna pay like 1.5 for like a townhouse
new york it's crazy you come to miami
for 1.5 and you're liking them you're
not you're no you're you're living in
anything you live in a studio you live
in lavish
so like i mean personally myself i want
i want to give it you know some time for
it to play out because definitely i
think real estate would be the play kind
of to just like diversify a little bit
um but when it came to like all those
nfc stuff like for me it's just like a
red flag it's like anything that comes
out that fast like it's dyed out you've
seen how like nobody's really been
talking yeah no no i mean that crypto it
went down like i don't know how much oh
bro don't even talk about it
i'm down right now on crypto like
like like like seven to eighty percent
like a lot yeah yeah i'm i'll be crying
i'm down bad right now so i mean back to
your family so you said your family is
supportive of you which that's awesome
bro like for real like bro well i'm
telling you a lot of people wish they
had that i thank god for that bro i
think what about your boys like your
friends because you told me you had a
youtube team squad or whatever like what
what are they up to uh well one of them
um
it's uh one of them is like his name is
frank shout out to franco um
he's into e-commerce he started
e-commerce with me as well like me when
i started forex
to be he's the type he was on the right
rich poured that that really changed our
whole mindset we were those type of kids
yeah 21 you're not really thinking about
the future like bro there's people at 25
still living with their parents you know
me and him are like the
like from the group the certain people
from the group it's like me and him are
like we're trying to be better like we
don't like we have everything we need
our parent supporters with everything we
need but we just want that lifestyle you
know we want the nice cars we want the
nice apartments we want all this
and yeah we just on that and like
people are our age not really thinking
about like
what's gonna happen a couple years from
now and we just want to live by
ourselves you know we want that
lifestyle we want all the cars and like
are you still like boys with the same
guys or no yeah yeah but it's just like
you know when you like this you have a
group of friends like you talk more to
one than the other like it's seven of us
so me and him are probably i'll say
we're probably the closest one and
another one as well
and um no no none of them trade you're
the only trader no yeah i'm the only
trader and he's like and and they
support you they're like oh cool yeah
they're all cool with it i remember i'm
proud of you i love my boys brother they
they didn't support me at all
nobody's avoiding me like are you still
friends with like the same people or no
no yeah and then now they're hitting me
they're like yo what's up yeah
and i'm like yo
so i want to touch up really fast back
on what you were saying july 23rd right
so kind of like the wardrobe you got
coming so like
that's a milestone you're setting for
yourself right so that that that could
be you know something something that you
you're coming you've been coming out
there for two years right
i personally i see you're excited right
so i personally myself i've set myself
very big milestones and
they get there on time or before maybe a
little bit late
and i don't want to say when i get them
i'm not satisfied but it's just like wow
like that's it you got me like i feel
like damn all right what's next you got
me and i raised that bar every single
time shout out to raul because every
single time i hit a milestone i feel
like a piece of [__] yes because raul
just comes in he's like all right that's
cute because
he's setting these milestones that are
like so high right so like literally the
level up is ridiculous so like other
than your you know the the wedge are you
trying to get what other milestones
would you say well first of all have you
hit any milestones yet
like like wasn't in that that you've hit
and have you felt that way i feel like
i feel like that first that would be my
first milestone like the first 20k
withdrawal because like i said i've
never really made that honestly that
would be like
five months of me working in
construction you know
and like i feel like as a human being i
feel like you're never content with what
you make i feel like humans always want
more and more and more
so let's say i mean
i guess you know when you're financially
free let's say okay i own five
properties now you always want more you
know
like let's say i got seven properties
like yeah you're always gonna want more
i feel like i guess when i when i pass
that financial freedom line because it
always goes up like once i pass it i
feel like i'll be content with her but
you always want more all the time you're
always going to want more and more more
and yeah once i pass that i feel like
i think i'll make it even though i know
i'm going to want more yeah of course
i'm encouraging more everything like for
me like if i can like suggest you
something reach for like 100k withdrawal
reach for something crazy no yeah so
once you get the 50k wardrobe you're
disappointed so then you go after the
200 300 like bro i'm telling you bro was
a master at that like when he had bro
the other day he had the i think it was
like a 100k trade oh yeah somebody said
his phone is like all right cool
that's it that's what i got to do just
like that and i'm just like
what do i do you know what i mean it's
just like what what goal do i say you
get me but that just shows you like if
you're putting in the work you're taking
the risk like you're doing everything
you have to do like bro like right now
you're in a great position because
you're locking like you're locked you're
focused like like you're locked in you
got me like nobody's coming in and
nobody's [__] with you like bro like
this doesn't matter you got me and like
i feel like everybody in my circle is in
the same position because if you're
around people that are not locked in
yeah they're going to come in they're
going to shake you up and it kind of you
know it sucks yeah i mean because you
kind of have to push people away but i
push a lot of people away a lot of great
people you got to do what you got to do
you got to do what you got to do if i
were to suggest to you something bro
it'd be like don't
don't set yourself short you get me like
trust me super cliche the sky is the
limit but i'm being for real i mean like
the opportunity out there i'm not an
alien i promise you you call me i
promise i'm a cool guy right obviously
like we can see yeah we could go eat
after here is it still early yeah we
could go eat all right um but yeah bro
that that's kind of something that like
i i i would tell you but bro i i
appreciate you trust me i appreciate you
coming out here kind of dropping these
gems um you know i'm glad the bootcamp
really did dude it did bro i'm telling
you whoever wants to grab that don't
hesitate really buy that like i'll
really help you okay change the training
away i didn't pay him for this it's not
a paid promotion this is kind of he's
coming from the heart everybody's i
promise you yeah all right so i mean bro
we'll get you back on july 20th you're
gonna see bro i'm not lying bro no i got
no data you trust me
so i appreciate you fernando coming out
hope to see you guys in the next episode
and take it easy guys i'll see